Guide to the Lester Sharp lantern slide collection, [19--]
Sharp, Lester lantern slide collection, [19--]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lester Sharp lantern slide collection, [19--]
6690
Lester W.(Lester Whyland), Sharp b.1887,
.6 cubic ft.
Black and white glass lantern slides.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Black and white glass lantern slides of portaits of various botanists from the 1500s-1900s, used by Professor Sharp in his lectures.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Botany, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Black and white glass lantern slides of portaits of various botanists from the 1500s-1900s, used by Professor Sharp in his lectures.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sharp, Lester W.b.1887,; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Scientists.; Botany.
Form and Genre Terms:
Portraits.; Lantern slides.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
A set of slides prepared by Barbara McClintock and Lester Sharp for the course on cytology at Cornell University was sent from Cornell to the Hunt Institute for Botanical Documentation at Carnegie Mellon University.
CONTAINER LIST
- Ernst Abbe, 1845-1905 (Box 1)
- Abbe (Box 1)
- G.G. Agardh, 1813-1901 (Box 1)
- Louis Agassiz (Box 1)
- Aristotle (Box 1)
- Geo. F. Atkinson, 1854-1918 (Box 1)
- von Baer, 1792-1876 (Box 1)
- Sir Joseph Banks, 1743-1820 (Box 1)
- C.R. Barnes, 1858-1910 (Box 1)
- Gaspard Bauhin, 1560-1624 (Box 1)
- John Jakob Bausch, Henry Lomb (Box 1)
- Edward Bausch, 1854-1944 (Box 1)
- Edward Bausch, William Busch, Carl Lomb, A.E. Drescher, 1833-1895 (Box 1)
- M.S. Bebb, 1833-1895 (Box 1)
- John Belling, 1866-1933 (Box 1)
- George Bentham, 1800-1884 (Box 1)
- Charles E. Bessey, 1845-1915 (Box 1)
- A.F. Blakeslee, ca. 1926 (Box 1)
- Edoardo Bornet, 1828-1911 (Box 1)
- Theodor Boveri, 1862-1915 (Box 1)
- Theodor Boveri, 1862-1915 (Box 1)
- Alex Braun, 1805-1877 (Box 1)
- W.B. Brierley, ca. 1930 (Box 1)
- Robert Brown, 1773-1858 (Box 1)
- Robert Brown, 1773-1858 (Box 1)
- Buffon, 1707-1788 (Box 1)
- Luther Burbank (Box 1)
- T.J. Burrill, 1839-1916 (Box 1)
- Wm. M. Canby, 1831-1904 (Box 1)
- A. Cesalpino, 1519-1603 (Box 1)
- A. Cesalpino, 1519-1603 (Box 1)
- Robert T. Clausen, ca. 1941 (Box 1)
- R.E. Cleland, ca. 1926 (Box 1)
- Charles Joseph Chamberlain (Box 1)
- C.J. Chamberlain, ca. 1923 (Box 1)
- A.W. Chapman, 1809-1899 (Box 1)
- F. Cohn, 1828-1898 (Box 1)
- C. Conzatti, ca. 1926 (Box 1)
- Capt. James Cook, 1728-1779 (Box 1)
- Valerius Cordus, 1515-1544 (Box 1)
- John Merle Coulter (Box 1)
- John M. Coulter (Box 1)
- G. Curvier, 1769-1832 (Box 1)
- Wm. Darlington, 1782-1863 (Box 1)
- Charles Darwin, 1809-1882, ca. 1880 (Box 1)
- Charles Darwin and sister, Catherine (Box 1)
- Charles Darwin, ca. 1854 (Box 1)
- C. Darwin (Box 1)
- C. Darwin (Box 1)
- C. Darwin (Box 1)
- Mrs. Darwin (Box 1)
- Erasmus Darwin, 1731-1802 (Box 1)
- DeBary, H.A., 1831-1888 (Box 1)
- G. B. Detoni, 1864-1924 (Box 1)
- Hugo DeVries, ca. 1904 (Box 1)
- Hugo DeVries, 1848-1935 (Box 1)
- Rembert Dodoens, 1517-1585 (Box 1)
- W.R. Dudley (Box 1)
- Felix Dujardin, 1801-1860 (Box 1)
- Arthur J. Eames, ca. 1941 (Box 1)
- Paul Ehrlich, 1854-1915 (Box 1)
- A.W. Eichler (Box 1)
- John Einset, ca. 1941 (Box 1)
- J.B. Ellis, 1829-? (Box 1)
- R.A. Emerson, ca. 1937 (Box 1)
- George Engelmann, 1809-1884 (Box 1)
- A. Engler (Box 1)
- A. Engler, 1844- (Box 1)
- B. E. Fernow (Box 1)
- Walther Flemming, 1843-1905 (Box 1)
- Leonhard Fuchs, 1501-1566 (Box 1)
- R. Ruggles Gates (Box 1)
- John Gerard, 1545-1607 (Box 1)
- J. Von Gerlach, 1820-1896 (Box 1)
- Konrad Gesner, 1516-1565 (Box 1)
- K. Goebel, 1855-1932 (Box 1)
- Karl von Goebel, 1855-1932 (Box 1)
- J.W. Goethe, 1749-1832 (Box 1)
- C. Golgi, 1844-1926 (Box 1)
- Asa Gray, 1810-1888 ca. 1841 (Box 2)
- Asa Gray, ca. 1867 (Box 2)
- Asa Gray, ca. 1886 (Box 2)
- E.L. Greene, 1843-1915 (Box 2)
- J.M Greenman, ca. 1929 (Box 2)
- V. Gregoire, 1870-1938 ca. 1925 (Box 2)
- V. Gregoire, ca. 1919 (Box 2)
- V. Gregoire, ca. 1923 (Box 2)
- Nehemiah Grew, 1641-1712 (Box 2)
- L. Guignard, 1852-1928 (Box 2)
- G. Haberlandt, 1854-1945 (Box 2)
- Ernst Haeckel, 1834-1919 (Box 2)
- Ernst Haeckel (Box 2)
- Stephen Hales, 1677-1761 (Box 2)
- R. A. Harper, B. Nemec, G. Tischler, ca. 1926 (Box 2)
- Queen Hatshepsut (Hatasu), ca. 1500 B.C.E. (Box 2)
- W.H. Harvey, 1811-1866 (Box 2)
- J.S. Henslow, 1796-1861 (Box 2)
- Henslow (Box 2)
- O. Hertwig (Box 2)
- Oscar Hertwig, 1849-1922 (Box 2)
- F. Hildebrand, 1835-1915 (Box 2)
- John Hill, 1716-1775 (Box 2)
- A.S. Hitchcock, ca. 1930 (Box 2)
- W. Hofmeister, 1824-1877 (Box 2)
- W. Hofmeister (Box 2)
- W. Hofmeister (Box 2)
- Robert Hooke, 1635-1703 (Box 2)
- J.D. Hooker, 1817-1911 (Box 2)
- J.D. Hooker (Box 2)
- W.J. Hooker, 1785-1865 (Box 2)
- J. Howell, 1842-1912 (Box 2)
- J.H. Huxley, 1825-1895 (Box 2)
- J.H. Huxley (Box 2)
- S. Ikeno, ca. 1924 (Box 2)
- Zacharias Janssen (Box 2)
- Jena (Box 2)
- W. Johannsen, 1857-1927 (Box 2)
- Ludwig Jost (Box 2)
- H.O. Juel (Box 2)
- H.O. Juel, ca. 1923 (Box 2)
- Jungen, Gregoire, Muller, Martens, ca. 1930 (Box 2)
- B.P. Kaufmann, ca. 1926 (Box 2)
- H. Klebahn, ca. 1930 (Box 2)
- G. Klebs, 1855- (Box 2)
- Hans Kniep (Box 2)
- Lewis Knudson, ca. 1936 (Box 2)
- Robert Koch, 1843-1910 (Box 2)
- von Koelliken, 1817-1905 (Box 2)
- Lamarck, 1744-1829 (Box 2)
- Lamarck (Box 2)
- Leeuwenhoek, 1632-1723 (Box 2)
- John Lindley, 1799-1865 (Box 2)
- Linnaeus, 1707-1778 (Box 2)
- Linnaeus (Box 2)
- Sir Joseph Lister, 1827-1912 (Box 2)
- Francis E. Lloyd (Box 2)
- F.E. Lloyd (Box 2)
- J.P. Lotsy (Box 2)
- H. Lundegardh, N. Johansson (Box 2)
- C. Lyell, 1797-1875 (Box 2)
- M. Malpighi, 1628-1694 (Box 2)
- M. Malpighi (Box 2)
- G. Massee (Box 2)
- Paul Mayer, 1848-1923 (Box 2)
- C.E. McClung, 1870-1945 (Box 2)
- Mendel, G., 1822-1884 (Box 2)
- Arthur Meyer, 1850-1922 (Box 2)
- F.A. Michaux, d. 1855 (Box 2)
- Hugo von Mohl, 1805-1872 (Box 2)
- Hugo von Mohl (Box 2)
- Hans Molisch (Box 2)
- Thomas Hunt Morgan, 1866-1945 (Box 2)
- Robert Morison, 1620-1683 (Box 2)
- G. H. E. Muhlenberg, 1753-1815 (Box 2)
- Herbert J. Muller, ca. 1946 (Box 2)
- Carl Nageli, 1817-1891 (Box 3)
- A.G. Nathorst, 1850-1921 (Box 3)
- S. Nawaschin, 1857-1930 (Box 3)
- Sergei Nawaschin (Box 3)
- S. Nawaschin (Box 3)
- Aven Nelson, ca. 1929 (Box 3)
- Otto Nordstedt, 1838-1924 (Box 3)
- Thomas Nuttall, 1786-1859 (Box 3)
- Mathias de l'Obel, 1538-1616 (Box 3)
- Fredrich Oltmanns (Box 3)
- V.I. Palladin (Box 3)
- J. Parkin, A.J. Eames, ca. 1930 (Box 3)
- John Parkinson, 1567-1650 (Box 3)
- Louis Pasteur, 1822-1895 (Box 3)
- Loren C. Petry, ca. 1931 (Box 3)
- Pfeffer (Box 3)
- Pfeffer, 1845- (Box 3)
- A. N. Prentiso, 1836-1896 (Box 3)
- Pringsheim, 1823-1894 (Box 3)
- Purkinje, 1787-1869 (Box 3)
- C. S. Rafinesque (Box 3)
- L. F. Randolph, ca. 1941 (Box 3)
- L. F. Randolph, ca. 1936 (Box 3)
- L. F. and F.R. Randolph, ca. 1941 (Box 3)
- John Ray, 1627-1705 (Box 3)
- John Ray, 1628-1705 (Box 3)
- F. Redi, 1626-1697 (Box 3)
- G. J. Romanes (Box 3)
- O. Rosenberg, ca. 1927 (Box 3)
- W. W. Rowlee (Box 3)
- Julius von Sachs, 1832-1897 (Box 3)
- Y. St. Hilaire, 1772-1844 (Box 3)
- E. R. Saunders (Box 3)
- Scheuchzer (Box 3)
- A.F.W. Schimper, 1856-1901 (Box 3)
- Schleiden, M.J., 1804-1881 (Box 3)
- Max Schultz, 1825-1874 (Box 3)
- Th. Schwann, 1810-1882 (Box 3)
- L.D. de Schweinitz, 1780-1834 (Box 3)
- Simon Schwendener, 1829-1919 (Box 3)
- Wm. Seifriz, C. Zirkle, ca. 1926 (Box 3)
- A. C. Seward, ca. 1930 (Box 3)
- L.W. Sharp, ca. 1939 (Box 3)
- Lester W. Sharp, ca. 1930 (Box 3)
- Spallanzani, 1729-1799 (Box 3)
- C. A. Spencer (Box 3)
- Herbert Spencer, 1820-1903 (Box 3)
- Eduard Strasburger, 1844-1912 (Box 3)
- Strasburger (Box 3)
- Strasburger (Box 3)
- W.R. Taylor, ca. 1926 (Box 3)
- Theophrastus (Box 3)
- Gustave Thuret, 1817-1875 (Box 3)
- van Tieghenn, 1839-1914 (Box 3)
- Georg Tischler (Box 3)
- Robert B. Tolles, 1824-1883 (Box 3)
- John Torrey, 1796-1876 (Box 3)
- L. R. Tulasne (Box 3)
- L.M. Underwood, 1853-1907 (Box 3)
- Urban (Box 3)
- E. Van Beneden, 1845-1910 (Box 3)
- Geo Vasey, 1822-1893 (Box 3)
- S.H. Vines (Box 3)
- Rudolph Virchow, 1821-1903 (Box 3)
- W. Waldeyer (Box 3)
- A.R. Wallace, 1923-1913 (Box 3)
- H. Marshall Ward, 1854-1906 (Box 3)
- S. Watson, 1826-1892 (Box 3)
- Weismann, A., 1834-1914 (Box 3)
- A. Weismann (Box 3)
- R. von Wettstein (Box 3)
- J. Wiesner, 1838- (Box 3)
- N. Wille, 1858-1924 (Box 3)
- W.C. Williamson, 1816-1895 (Box 3)
- E. B. Wilson, 1856-1939 ca. 1921 (Box 3)
- E. B. Wilson, ca. 1921 (Box 3)
- O. Winge J. Clausen (Box 3)
- University of Penn. - Botanical Gardens and Dorimitory, 1894 (Box 3)